aftvnews.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy Policy | AFTVnews

AFTVnews is a news and information website located in the United States with the website address http://www.aftvnews.com.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

##### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it so that an avatar can be displayed. The Gravatar service privacy policy is at [automattic.com/privacy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. If you leave a comment on our site your name, email address, and website will be saved in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

##### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

##### Analytics

When you visit AFTVnews, some information is automatically saved by our server, which is hosted by [SiteGround](https://www.siteground.com/terms.htm) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.siteground.com/privacy.htm)), as well as by third-party services including [Google Analytics](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) ([Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)). That data includes: Your IP address, The name of the page visited, The date and time of that visit, Your browser type and version, Your operating system, and A referring URL, if applicable (the page you’d previously visited). This data helps us track response to articles, understand the demographics of visitors to this site, and generally do a better job of understanding and serving our audience.

## Who we share your data with

##### Advertising

AFTVnews works with several third-party advertising services. These companies may use information about your visits to this website and others in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may interest you. Our advertising partners include: [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)), [Ziff Davis](http://www.ziffdavistech.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.ziffdavis.com/privacy-policy)), and [Amazon Advertising Program](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)).

##### Affiliate Networks

AFTVnews works with several third-party affiliate revenue services. These companies may use information about you when you click an affiliate link on this site to provide advertisements about goods and services that may interest you. Our affiliate partners include: [Amazon Affiliate Program](https://affiliate-program.amazon.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496)), [eBay Partner Network](https://partnernetwork.ebay.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://partnernetwork.ebay.com/legal/?afsrc=1&rmvSB=true#a6)), [Consumer Junction](http://www.cj.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://www.conversantmedia.com/legal/privacy)), [Rakuten](https://rakutenmarketing.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://rakutenmarketing.com/legal-notices/website-privacy-policy)), [Impact](https://impact.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://impact.com/privacy-policy/)), and [Skimlinks](https://skimlinks.com/) ([Privacy Policy](https://skimlinks.com/pages/privacy-policy#publishers)).

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Contact information

You can reach us by sending an email to contact@aftvnews.com
